<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Personal on keathley.co</title>
    <link>https://www.keathley.co/tags/personal/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Personal on keathley.co</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 07:17:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.keathley.co/tags/personal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>16 Years Later</title>
      <link>https://www.keathley.co/posts/16-anniversary/16-anniversary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 07:17:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.keathley.co/posts/16-anniversary/16-anniversary/</guid>
      <description>Deana and I met in 2006 when I had just moved to North Carolina following Hurricane Katrina. I was at a friend’s apartment to play board games and she was there to borrow a movie. I added her on AIM (rest in peace) and we started talking there. I still have the transcript of those couple months of conversations and it’s hilarious. We would start dating almost a month after that exactly on my birthday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on the Past</title>
      <link>https://www.keathley.co/posts/thoughts-on-the-past/thoughts-on-the-past/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 09:35:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.keathley.co/posts/thoughts-on-the-past/thoughts-on-the-past/</guid>
      <description>I was born in a small town in southeast Missouri called ‘Poplar Bluff’. My early memories are almost exclusively happy. I remember looking up at the counter tops as I walked around the kitchen and living room. My mom, Penny, was making a grilled cheese sandwich and Perry Mason was on the television in the living room. My dad, Kenneth, was the pastor of Maud Street Baptist church at the time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philosophy of Life</title>
      <link>https://www.keathley.co/posts/life-philosophy/life-philosophy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 10:04:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.keathley.co/posts/life-philosophy/life-philosophy/</guid>
      <description>Personal Vision Live one day at a time engaged and solving problems with empathy and love for others and an alignment and love for God. Keep an open hand with everything else knowing that we come from nothing and to nothing we return.
Core Values Empathy Innovation Fun Community Growth Beliefs We enter the world with nothing and exit with nothing. Once you understand that and stop trying to hold onto things you will be able to enjoy them.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
